{
    "subject": "Ishir\u014d_Honda",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Godzilla__1954_film_",
    "human_readable": "Ishir\u014d Honda created the Godzilla (1954) film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9534409642219543,
            "question": "Who created the Godzilla (1954) film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7433847784996033,
            "question": "What genre does the Godzilla (1954) film belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7183758020401001,
            "question": "Besides Godzilla, what other monsters did Ishir\u014d Honda create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6854325532913208,
            "question": "What year was the Godzilla film released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4902289807796478,
            "question": "How did the Godzilla film impact Japanese cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47173288464546204,
            "question": "What is the name of the famous monster featured in the 1954 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4671134352684021,
            "question": "Was Godzilla a successful film upon release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3547239899635315,
            "question": "What are some recurring themes in Godzilla films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3411564230918884,
            "question": "Ishir\u014d Honda is known for what type of work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0475526824593544,
            "question": "Name a director who worked on a kaiju film."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ishir\u014d Honda created the Godzilla (1954) film.",
            "html": "yago_4790_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ishir\u014d Honda is known for what type of work?",
            "html": "yago_4790_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some recurring themes in Godzilla films?",
            "html": "yago_4790_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Godzilla a successful film upon release?",
            "html": "yago_4790_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4790_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that Ishir\u014d Honda directed the 1954 Godzilla film, supporting the statement that Ishir\u014d Honda created the Godzilla (1954) film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}